<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="ans">

     <item>
        A computer system is a combination of memory,
         CPU, peripheral devices that are connected to it,
         and OS (Operating System).
    </item>

    <item>
        A microprocessor is an integrated circuit having all the functionality
        of a central processing unit of a PC.
    </item>

    <item>
        A programming language is a collection of grammar rules for giving
        instructions to computer or computing devices in order to perform achieve task.
    </item>

    <item>
        Networking is used to connect or operate with a network.
        It is the process of creating and using wired or wireless networks for exchanging information,
        ideas, files, and other electronic communication.
    </item>

    <item>
        Layer 1 – Physical
        Layer 2 – Data Link Layer
        Layer 3 – Network
        Layer 4 – Transport
        Layer 5 – Session
        Layer 6 – Presentation
        Layer 7- Application
    </item>

    <item>
        An array is a container that keeps a specific number of
        similar data types.
    </item>

    <item>
        A constructor is a method that is used to create a class object.
    </item>

    <item>
        Artificial Intelligence or machine intelligence
        is a common term that is used to build smart machines capable of performing tasks. The main aim of AI is to solve problems in a way that are better and faster.
    </item>

    <item>
        Machine Learning is a system that can learn from an excellent
        example through self-improvement and without
        being explicitly coded by a programmer.
    </item>

    <item>
        Deep learning is computer software that mimics
        the network of neurons in a brain. It is
        a subset of machine learning and is called
        deep learning because it makes use of
        deep neural networks.
    </item>

    <item>
        Routing is the process to find the path on
        which the information or data can pass from the
        source to its destination. The device by which
        routing is done is called Routers.
    </item>

    <item>
        It is a Virtual LAN network which is used to
        make a separate domain in a single switch.
    </item>
    <item>
        Static IP address will not change over time and is
        reserved statically whereas dynamic IP address changes
        each time when you connect to the Internet.
    </item>

    <item>
        The P2P network is a distributed and decentralized
        network where individual nodes i.e. Peers in the networks
        act as both suppliers and consumers of the resources.
    </item>

    <item>
        WWW or World Wide Web is a method of
        accessing information using internet media.
    </item>

    <item>
        An algorithm is a rule or step-by-step
        process that must be followed in order to
        solve a particular problem.
    </item>

    <item>
        An Operating system (OS) is a software that
        acts as an interface between the end-user
        and computer hardware. Every computer must have at least one OS to run other programs.
    </item>

    <item>
        IEEE 802.11
    </item>

    <item>
        A protocol enables two devices to connect and
        transmit the information or data to one another.
    </item>

    <item>
        DNS is an internet service that translates domain names
        into IP addresses. Anything connected to the internet i.e. mobile phones, laptops, websites etc. has an IP address that is uniquely defined.
    </item>

    </string-array>
    </resources>